Guide to the Bebe Moore Campbell Papers, 1956-2008 SC.2017.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Tour Schedules, 1993-2005; VIII.
  - Tour Schedule, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 266)
  - Tour Schedule, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 267-269)
  - Tour Schedule, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 270-273)
  - Tour Schedule, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 274)
  - Tour Schedule, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 275)
  - Tour Schedule, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 276-277)
  - Tour Schedule, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Tour Schedule, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 279)
  - Tour Schedule, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 280-281)
  - Tour Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 282)
- Contracts, 1987-2005; IX.
  - Speaking Contracts, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 283)
  - Speaking Contracts, 1996-2004 (Box 26, Folder 284)
  - Speaking Confirmation Agreements, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 285)
  - Random House Contracts, 1987-1998 (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Publishing Contracts, 1996-2005 (Box 26, Folder 287)
  - Permission Request, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - Royalty Information, Your Blues Ain't Like Mine, 1989-1998 (Box 27, Folder 289-290)
  - Royalty Information, Brothers and Sisters, 1992-1998 (Box 27, Folder 291-292)
  - Royalty Information, Singing in the Comeback Choir, 1995-2002 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Royalty Information, 72 Hour Hold, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - Foreign Publishing Contracts, 1994-2005 (Box 27, Folder 295-296)
  - Rights Contracts, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 297)
- Financial Information, 1994-2006; X.
  - 72 Hour Hold Pre-Orders, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 298)
  - Expenses, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Invoices and Receipts, 1996-2006 (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Airline Statements, 1994-1997 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Airline Statements, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Invoices and Receipts, 1997-2005 (Box 28, Folder 303)
- Personal Papers, 1970-2008; XI.
  - Daily Planner, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 308-319)
  - Daily Planner, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 320-321)
  - Calenders, 1996-2003 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Treatment Schedules, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 323)
  - Photographs, 1990-c2005 (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Name Lists, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 325)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Passports, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Memorials, 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 328)